{
    "subject": "resource/Survival_of_the_Fittest_(song)",
    "predicate": "ontology/recordLabel",
    "object": "resource/Loud_Records",
    "human_readable": "The song 'Survival of the Fittest' is released by Loud Records.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9040855169296265,
            "question": "Which record label released the song 'Survival of the Fittest'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8124800324440002,
            "question": "Are there any other songs by Loud Records that are similar to 'Survival of the Fittest'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.760158121585846,
            "question": "Who performed the song 'Survival of the Fittest'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7209879159927368,
            "question": "When was 'Survival of the Fittest' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6710595488548279,
            "question": "What is the name of the song released by Loud Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6315398812294006,
            "question": "Is 'Survival of the Fittest' a rap song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4132339060306549,
            "question": "How was 'Survival of the Fittest' received by critics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3978930115699768,
            "question": "What impact did 'Survival of the Fittest' have on popular music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3519560694694519,
            "question": "Were there any notable collaborations on 'Survival of the Fittest'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2976630926132202,
            "question": "What genre is associated with Loud Records?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The song 'Survival of the Fittest' is released by Loud Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1884_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable collaborations on 'Survival of the Fittest'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1884_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did 'Survival of the Fittest' have on popular music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1884_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How was 'Survival of the Fittest' received by critics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1884_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1884_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1884_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1884_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1884_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1884_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1884_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1884_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1884_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1884_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1884_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"Survival of the Fittest\" was released as a single from Mobb Deep's album \"The Infamous\" on May 29, 1995, by Loud Records. This information supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}